"""
Dictionary extracted from https://the-trivia-api.com/

"""

music = [
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff30",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Nicki Minaj",
            "Neil Young",
            "Eric Clapton"
        ],
        "question": "Which American singer released the song 'You Rock My World'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Divinyls",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "62506444e12f6dec240bdfa6",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Vicki Sue Robinson",
            "Frankie Goes to Hollywood",
            "Stacey Q"
        ],
        "question": "'I Touch Myself' was a one hit wonder in 1990 by which artist?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "one_hit_wonders"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Spice Girls",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b18",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Editors",
            "Cradle of Filth",
            "The Sweet"
        ],
        "question": "Which band includes 'Melanie Brown'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "What's Up",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "625064dae12f6dec240bdfd2",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Rapper's Delight",
            "Seasons in the Sun",
            "I Melt With You"
        ],
        "question": "What song did 4 Non Blondes have a hit with in 1992?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "one_hit_wonders",
            "1990's"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Rihanna",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe8f",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Drake",
            "Nicki Minaj",
            "Ricky Martin"
        ],
        "question": "Which singer released the song 'Disturbia'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Metallica",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c8b",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Alice Cooper",
            "The Pussycat Dolls",
            "Three 6 Mafia"
        ],
        "question": "Which American heavy metal band released the studio album 'Master of Puppets'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Radiohead",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950bfc",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Goldfrapp",
            "Cream",
            "Girls Aloud"
        ],
        "question": "Which English rock band released the studio album 'Kid A'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "\"American Pie\" by Don McLean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbae",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"All Star\" by Smash Mouth",
            "\"I'll Make a Man Out of You\" by Donny Osmond",
            "\"I Write Sins Not Tragedies\" by Panic! at the Disco"
        ],
        "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"A long, long time ago / I can still remember how / That music used to make me smile...\"?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "lyrics"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Katy Perry",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fdd9",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Madonna",
            "Nicki Minaj",
            "Lady Gaga"
        ],
        "question": "Which American singer released the song 'Last Friday Night (T.G.I.F.)'?",
        "tags": [
            "songs"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "\"Werewolves of London\" by Warren Zevon",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbba",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"In da Club\" by 50 Cent",
            "\"Crazy Train\" by Ozzy Osbourne",
            "\"Baby Got Back\" by Sir Mix-a-Lot"
        ],
        "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"I saw a werewolf with a Chinese menu in his hand...\"?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "lyrics"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "\"Welcome to the Black Parade\" by My Chemical Romance",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fbb9",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"Let's Go Crazy\" by Prince and The Revolution",
            "\"Immigrant Song\" by Led Zeppelin",
            "\"Rapper's Delight\" by Sugarhill Gang"
        ],
        "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"When I was a young boy / My father took me into the city...\"?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "lyrics"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Green Day",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950dc3",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Mastodon",
            "Animal Collective",
            "Fall Out Boy"
        ],
        "question": "Which band includes 'Billie Joe Armstrong'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Guns N Roses",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd4a",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Sex Pistols",
            "The Ramones",
            "The Clash"
        ],
        "question": "With Which Rock Band Does \"Slash\" Play Guitar?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "The Cranberries",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b10",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "The Corrs",
            "Boyzone",
            "Thin Lizzy"
        ],
        "question": "Which Irish rock band released the single 'Zombie'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Eurythmics",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b50",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Level 42",
            "Feeder",
            "Uriah Heep"
        ],
        "question": "Which British music duo released the song 'Sweet Dreams (Are Made of This)'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "The Doors",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950d80",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Styx",
            "The Pussycat Dolls",
            "Three 6 Mafia"
        ],
        "question": "Which band includes 'Jim Morrison'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Graceland",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fda9",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Neverland",
            "Jackson Ranch",
            "Amity"
        ],
        "question": "What Was The Name Of Elvis Presley's Home?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Michael Jackson",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff31",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Nicki Minaj",
            "Neil Young",
            "Eric Clapton"
        ],
        "question": "'You Are Not Alone' is a song by which musician?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Coldplay",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950da5",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Level 42",
            "Deep Purple",
            "Feeder"
        ],
        "question": "Which band includes 'Chris Martin'?",
        "tags": [
            "people"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "\"The House of the Rising Sun\" by The Animals",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb9c",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"Circle of Life\" by Elton John",
            "\"Yo Home to Bel-Air\"",
            "\"SpongeBob SquarePants Theme\" by Painty the Pirate"
        ],
        "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"There is a house in New Orleans...\"?",
        "tags": [
            "lyrics"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Prince",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd55",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "James Brown",
            "Chris Brown",
            "Jamiroquai"
        ],
        "question": "With Which Artist Is The Funk Band 'The New Power Generation' Associated?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "ABBA",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c30",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "In Flames",
            "HammerFall",
            "Katatonia"
        ],
        "question": "Which Swedish pop group released the song 'Waterloo'?",
        "tags": [
            "pop_music",
            "general_knowledge"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Nicki Minaj",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fddb",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Hikaru Utada",
            "Alanis Morissette",
            "Ludacris"
        ],
        "question": "Which singer released the song 'Bitch I'm Madonna'?",
        "tags": [
            "songs"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Radiohead",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950bf7",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Goldfrapp",
            "Cream",
            "Girls Aloud"
        ],
        "question": "Which English rock band released the song 'Creep'?",
        "tags": [
            "rock_music",
            "general_knowledge"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "\"Respect\" by Aretha Franklin",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb88",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"Baby Got Back\" by Sir Mix-a-Lot",
            "\"Pepper\" by Butthole Surfers",
            "\"Carry On Wayward Son\" by Kansas"
        ],
        "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"What you want, baby, I got it!\"?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "lyrics",
            "general_knowledge"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Kylie Minogue",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fef8",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Madonna",
            "Mika",
            "Hikaru Utada"
        ],
        "question": "Which Australian singer, recording artist, songwriter, showgirl, and actress released the song 'Spinning Around'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "\"No Scrubs\" by TLC",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb8f",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"Hooked on a Feeling\" by B.J. Thomas",
            "\"Rapper's Delight\" by Sugarhill Gang",
            "\"Fergalicious\" by Fergie and will.i.am."
        ],
        "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"A scrub is a guy that thinks he's fly and is also known as a busta.\"?",
        "tags": [
            "lyrics"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Foreigner",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff71",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Gotthard",
            "The Velvet Underground",
            "The Chicks"
        ],
        "question": "Which Band Had A 1985 Number One Hit With The Single “I Wanna Know What Love Is”?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Spice Girls",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b1d",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Editors",
            "Cradle of Filth",
            "The Sweet"
        ],
        "question": "Which band includes 'Melanie C'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "The Police",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b3c",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Level 42",
            "Wings",
            "Ultravox"
        ],
        "question": "Which band includes 'Sting'?",
        "tags": [
            "people"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Graceland",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fd9b",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Traceland",
            "Faceland",
            "Placeland"
        ],
        "question": "Which Paul Simon Album Won A Grammy For Album Of The Year In 1987?",
        "tags": [
            "music_albums"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "One Direction",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950ba7",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Level 42",
            "Orchestral Manoeuvres in the Dark",
            "Blur"
        ],
        "question": "Which English-Irish boy band released the studio album 'Up All Night'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "\"Truth Hurts\" by Lizzo",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb86",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"I'm Real (Murder Remix) by Jennifer Lopez and Ja Rule",
            "\"Old Man\" by Neil Young",
            "\"Chimpan-A to Chimpan-Z\" by Troy McClure"
        ],
        "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Why men great 'till they gotta be great?\"?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "lyrics"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Kraftwerk",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950377",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Rammstein",
            "Pink Floyd",
            "The Stranglers"
        ],
        "question": "Who Released The 70's Album Entitled Trans-Europe Express",
        "tags": [
            "1970's"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Eminem",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe8a",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Nicki Minaj",
            "Drake",
            "Ludacris"
        ],
        "question": "Which American rapper, producer and actor released the studio album 'The Marshall Mathers LP'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "David Bowie",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fee8",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Eric Clapton",
            "Madonna",
            "Mika"
        ],
        "question": "Which British musician performed under the alter ego 'Ziggy Stardust'?",
        "tags": [
            "pseudonyms",
            "people"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "David Bowie",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fef1",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Eric Clapton",
            "Elton John",
            "Sting"
        ],
        "question": "Which British musician released the studio album 'Hunky Dory'?",
        "tags": [
            "uk"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Elton John",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fea9",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Mika",
            "Madonna",
            "Eric Clapton"
        ],
        "question": "Which English rock singer-songwriter, composer and pianist performed the soundtrack album 'The Lion King'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Wings",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b9d",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Level 42",
            "Deep Purple",
            "The Chemical Brothers"
        ],
        "question": "Which British–American rock band led by Paul McCartney released the song 'Live and Let Die'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Pink Floyd",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950cbd",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Wings",
            "Rudimental",
            "The Alan Parsons Project"
        ],
        "question": "Which English rock band released the studio album 'Wish You Were Here'?",
        "tags": [
            "rock_music",
            "general_knowledge"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Queen",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94ff64",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Feeder",
            "The Clash",
            "Pink Floyd"
        ],
        "question": "Which British rock band released the single 'Another One Bites the Dust'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Tchaikovsky",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950340",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Handel",
            "Bach",
            "Schuberg"
        ],
        "question": "Who was the composer of 'The Nutcracker' ballet?",
        "tags": [
            "classical_music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "\"Fergalicious\" by Fergie and will.i.am.",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fb8d",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"Let's Go Crazy\" by Prince and The Revolution",
            "\"Old Man\" by Neil Young",
            "\"All Star\" by Smash Mouth"
        ],
        "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"Listen up, y'all, 'cause this is it, the beat that I'm bangin' is de-li-cious.\"?",
        "tags": [
            "lyrics"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "The Jimi Hendrix Experience",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b8c",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Poison",
            "The Pussycat Dolls",
            "Three 6 Mafia"
        ],
        "question": "Which English-American psychedelic rock band released the song 'Voodoo Child (Slight Return)'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "\"Hurt\" by Nine Inch Nails",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c347cc59eab6f94fba2",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "\"Hooked on a Feeling\" by B.J. Thomas",
            "\"Old Man\" by Neil Young",
            "\"I'll Make a Man Out of You\" by Donny Osmond"
        ],
        "question": "Which song begins with the lyrics: \"I hurt myself today / To see if I still feel / I focus on the pain / The only thing that's real...\"?",
        "tags": [
            "songs",
            "lyrics"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "David Bowie",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94feee",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Eric Clapton",
            "Madonna",
            "Mika"
        ],
        "question": "Which musician released the album '\"Heroes\"'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Beyoncé",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94feb9",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Madonna",
            "Drake",
            "Nicki Minaj"
        ],
        "question": "Which American singer, actress and record producer released the song 'Me, Myself and I'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Nirvana",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c397cc59eab6f950c1c",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Counting Crows",
            "Three 6 Mafia",
            "The Velvet Underground"
        ],
        "question": "Which American rock band released the song 'Come as You Are'?",
        "tags": [
            "rock_music"
        ],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Take That",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c387cc59eab6f950b04",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Talk Talk",
            "Feeder",
            "Bring Me the Horizon"
        ],
        "question": "Which band includes 'Gary Barlow'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    },
    {
        "category": "Music",
        "correctAnswer": "Eminem",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fe87",
        "incorrectAnswers": [
            "Nicki Minaj",
            "Drake",
            "Ludacris"
        ],
        "question": "Which American rapper, producer and actor released the studio album 'Encore'?",
        "tags": [],
        "type": "Multiple Choice"
    }
]
